<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dash_search_hint">Search</string>
    <string name="dash_lens_apps_title">Applications</string>
    <string name="dash_lens_other_title">Other</string>
    <string name="title_activity_preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lens_preferences">Search sources</string>
    <string name="title_activity_theme_preferences">Themes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dev_logs">Logs</string>
    <string name="pinned">has been pinned to the launcher</string>
    <string name="unpinned">has been unpinned from the launcher</string>
    <string name="notpinned">isn\'t pinned</string>
    <string name="alreadypinned">is already pinned</string>
    <string name="developed_by">Developed by Robin Jacobs</string>
    <string name="honourable_mentions">Honourable mentions</string>
    <string name="button_back">Back</string>
    <string name="button_about">About</string>
    <string name="button_contribute">Contribute</string>
    <string name="button_apply">Apply</string>

    <string-array name="edges">
        <item>Hide</item>
        <item>Top</item>
        <item>Right</item>
        <item>Bottom</item>
        <item>Left</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>
    <string name="pref_header_launcher">Launcher</string>
    <string name="pref_header_dash">Dash</string>
    <string name="pref_header_panel">Panel</string>
    <string name="pref_header_advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="pref_header_dev">Developer options</string>
    <string name="pref_header_functionality">Functionality</string>
    <string name="pref_header_appearance">Appearance</string>
    <string name="option_launchericon_size">Pinned icon size</string>
    <string name="hint_launchericon_size">How large icons for pinned apps should be. The slider goes from 48dip to 120dip, with the default (right in the middle) being 84dip.</string>
    <string name="option_panel_edge">Panel location</string>
    <string name="hint_panel_edge">To which screen edge the Panel should be attached.</string>
    <string name="option_launcher_edge">Launcher location</string>
    <string name="hint_launcher_edge">To which screen edge the Launcher should be attached.</string>
    <string name="option_widgets_enabled">Widgets</string>
    <string name="hint_widgets_enabled">Enable <b>experimental</b> (read: <b>broken</b>) widget support.\nThis is very experimental and not very usable in its current state.</string>
    <string name="option_dev_log_toaster">Log toasts</string>
    <string name="hint_dev_log_toaster">Show log items in toast messages.</string>
    <string name="option_customise">Customise</string>
    <string name="hint_customise">Customise the look and feel.</string>

    <string name="option_wallpaper">Wallpaper</string>
    <string name="hint_wallpaper">Change wallpaper</string>
    <string name="option_dash_ready_show">Open Dash by default</string>
    <string name="hint_dash_ready_show">The Dash will automatically be opened.</string>
    <string name="option_lenses">Search sources</string>
    <string name="hint_lenses">Choose which source searches you want to use and in which order you want their results to appear in the Dash. When you do a search in the Dash, your query is sent to all enabled lenses and their results are shown.</string>
    <string name="option_theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="hint_theme">Choose which Linux distribution you want DistroHopper to look like.</string>
    <string name="option_dev">Developer mode</string>
    <string name="hint_dev">Access debug logs and other technical information. Enabling this will negatively impact performance and stability.</string>
    <string name="option_dev_logs">Logs</string>
    <string name="hm_timvdstaaij_why">* Testing (If he doesn\'t manage to wreck it then it\'s probably safe for consumption by the rest of the world.)\n
        * Help with the dominant colour calculation function.</string>
    <string name="hm_todddavies_why">* I used his ProgressWheel component, since the default (round) Android ProgressBar component can\'t actually indicate progress.\n
        https://github.com/Todd-Davies/ProgressWheel/</string>
    <string name="hm_translators_name">The Translation Team</string>
    <string name="hm_translators_why">* A couple of people devoted time and effort to make this app available in their respective languages. I am grateful towards all of these people for their contributions to the project.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contribute">How can I contribute?</string>
    <string name="contribute_intro">A lot of time and hard work went into the development of this application. If you\'d like to help out, there are several ways in which you can do so.</string>
    <string name="contribute_translate_title">Translate</string>
    <string name="contribute_translate_description">DistroHopper is available in several languages. This is because volunteers provide the project with their translations. If DistroHopper has not been translated yet into your own language, and you understand English (and you have sufficient knowledge of the Linux desktop to understand some of the more Unity-related terms), then helping out with translations is a good way to help out.
        \nTranslations for DistroHopper are managed on Transifex. All you need to do is request to join a translation team. After that I will approve your request and you are good to go.</string>
    <string name="contribute_translate_go">Go to Transifex</string>
    <string name="contribute_bugs_title">Report bugs</string>
    <string name="contribute_bugs_description">If there is a bug in DistroHopper, that does not necessarily mean that I am aware of its existence. Developers are generally quite bad at testing their own applications as they will only use them in a way they are intended to be used. Some problems also only exist in certain specific circumstances (for example a certain device running a specific version of Android with some extra options enabled). So if you find a bug in DistroHopper (or if you have a feature request) you can help out by reporting it.
        \nBug reports for DistroHopper are kept on GitHub. If GitHub is too technical for you, you can also just send an e-mail to android-dev@robinj.be. Just make sure it\'s in English or Dutch. Please provide as much (relevant) information as possible.</string>
    <string name="contribute_bugs_go">Go to GitHub</string>
    <string name="contribute_donate_title">Donate</string>
    <string name="contribute_donate_description">If you want, you can also make a monetary donation to the developer. Donations are handled via PayPal. You will be able to pick the amount of money you\'d like to donate.
        \nNote: It\'s a donation. I am not selling anything, and you are not buying anything. Donations are greatly appreciated, but you will not gain any additional features because of it. All features of this application are available free of charge.</string>

    <string name="theme_elementary_res_panel_bfb_text">Applications</string>

    <string name="toast_sending_crash_report">Sending crash report...</string>
</resources>
